http://www.realniches.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
IMPORTANT DISCLOSURE This blog Realniches.com may be compensated to provide opinions on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though we receive compensation for our posts, reviews or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. We are independently owned and the opinions expressed here are our own. Visit Disclosure page for more details.
SetApp - Your Shortcut To Prime Apps For Mac.
HomeDepot.com - Special Offers At The Home Depot - Visit Now!
Get unlimited access to The Real Deal, the #1 source for real estate news. Click here to explore options that work for any budget.
Stop giving your hard earned money back! Deliver for DoorDash with your bike to save on gas, parking and tolls & keep what you earn. Apply today!
Pages
Contact
Disclosure
Privacy Policy
Archives
October 2020
September 2020
August 2020
Privacy Policy for realniches.com
The privacy of our visitors to realniches.com is important to us.
At realniches.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit realniches.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
We also use third party advertisements on realniches.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. Also, we may use Google’s “remarketing” service or any “remarketing” services to target our ads to you based on your prior use of the Site when you visit on other sites in Google’s content network or any other third party content network sites.
“Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.”
Copyright
- © 2005 - 2020 - www.realniches.com
